# MOK CHI HONG

+6016-420 7769 · mokchi2324@hotmail.com · https://joseph-portfolio-ugu2y6sala-as.a.run.app/ Butterworth, Penang, Malaysia

### FULL STACK WEB & MOBILE DEVELOPER

Full stack developer with 3 years of working experience in both mobile and web development. My proficient is in developing full stack web application using Laravel / Yii2 Framework, mobile application with Flutter and backend RESTful APIs. I specialized in creating user-friendly applications by writing clean, reusable and maintainable code. I'm passionate about staying updated with latest trend in web and mobile development. I have experience leading a team and also capable of working with minimal supervision. I love to accept new challenges and I'm a fast learner.

| SKILL |
|-------|
|-------|

| Flutter | PHP        | RESTful API  | Git    |
|---------|------------|--------------|--------|
| Laravel | TypeScript | MySQL        | Docker |
| Yii2    | ReactJS    | Tailwind CSS | YOLOv5 |

### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

### Silkron Technology Sdn Bhd Lead Software Engineer

Jan 2023 - Present

Responsibilities

- Lead and manage team by providing mentorship and guidance.
- Develop and maintain custom white label mobile application.
- Design, develop and maintain mobile application using Flutter framework.
- · CI/CD with GitHub action.
- Publish and maintain mobile application on Google play and Apple app store.
- Develop and integrate RESTful APIs into mobile app and document with OpenAPI, Swagger.
- Continuously optimize & monitor app and API performance to enhance user satisfaction and efficiency.
- Assign task and evaluate man-days for team.
- · Code base version control with Git and SVN.

#### Accomplishments:

- Revamp entire mobile app and cloud APIs legacy code base by writing clean and maintainable code to reduce bugs and errors.
- Develop and deploy various customize mobile app.
- Integrated various foreign payment such as LinePay, Paypay, PayPal, WeChat Pay.

### Silkron Technology Sdn Bhd Software Engineer

June 2021 - Jan 2023

### Responsibilities

- Design, develop and maintain web application using Yii2 Framework and JS.
- · Develop, maintain and deploy WeChat Mini Program.
- Al Model training with YOLOv5 object detection algorithm and image labeling using PaddleSeg.
- Develop and integrate RESTful APIs for WeChat mini program and mobile application.
- Design, develop and maintain mobile application using Flutter framework.
- · Code base version control with Git and SVN.

#### Accomplishments:

- Train AI model for smart fridge project which average has above 96% accuracy.
- Develop and deploy WeChat mini program for China client using WeChat H5 framework.

# Silkron Technology Sdn Bhd Internship

Jan 2021 - June 2021

Responsibilities

- Design, develop and maintain web-based application with MySQL, JS and Yii2 PHP Framework
- · Assist senior debug and solve web related issues.

# Zepheus Corporate Services Sdn Bhd Internship

June 2020 - Sept 2020

Responsibilities

• Design and develop responsive web-base secretary system using MySQL, JS, Jquery and Laravel PHP Framework.

### **EDUCATION**

### **University of Greenwich**

Bachelor Of Science (HONS) Computing

3.91 CGPA | 2019 - 2021

- · First class honours
- · Best student award
- Develop a fully functioning web-based comic website with Laravel and deploy it on Microsoft Azure.

## **SEGi College Penang**

Diploma In Information Technology

3.62 CGPA | 2016 - 2018

- Vice president of Multi-Tech Society
- Champion of SEGi Video Competition

### LANGUAGE

Chinese English Malay

### ADDITIONAL SKILL

GCP WeChat H5 Adobe packages Excel VBA
C# C++ Java Python